

# Contact

+66 97 063 2416 Skype: live:alax54321 alax54321@gmail.com http://linkedin.com/in/alaxaung-kyaw-kyaw-0115081b9 https://facebook.com/24625067 20550752

# Specialization & Skills

Software Engineering: Mobile Engineer, Frontend Engineer, System Engineer

Javascript (1 year), HTML5 (1 year), CSS (1 year), React (< 1 years), JQuery (1 year)

# Languages

English - Advanced Thai - Proficient Spanish - Beginner Burmese - Native

# **Aung Kyaw Kyaw Alax**

# Mobile Engineer, Frontend Engineer, System Engineer

Pangkok, Thailand

**Date of birth:** September 1st 1996 (25 years old)

Hello, I'm Alax, a self-taught, detail-oriented front-end developer. Primarily focus on writing efficient and clean code. I am proficient and experience working with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. Highly motivated and capable for collaborative and independent projects with emphasis on building user-friendly digital experiences and website development.

# **Work Experience**

# **Expatriate Liaison Officer**

Bumrungrad International Hospital -Full-time

Middle, Medical Services / Others, Medical Services / Pharmaceutical / Hospitals

Bangkok, Thailand

 Coordinated with more than 20 departments/clinics and liaised patients of 10 or more different nationalities with their appointments and procedures. • Mainly used English, Thai, Burmese vice versa in communications and interpretations to patients, internal staffs and teams. • Proficiently assisted and provided productive guidance VIP/ High-class patients with their schedules. • Proactively promoted and assured hospital health products, treatments and services. • Thoroughly studied, analyzed nature and requisites of expat patients and enhance expats market.

### **Inter Ops Officer (Myanmar Patient Liaison)**

Bumrungrad International Hospital -Full-time

Middle, Medical Services / Others, Medical Services / Pharmaceutical / Hospitals

Bangkok, Thailand

• Seamlessly interpreted in live or remote to conversations between healthcare providers and Myanmar patients with high accuracy. • Coordinated proactively with all related departments/clinics, nurses and staffs according to their appointments and procedures. • Displayed culture awareness in polished-manners, apparels and gestures to the patients. • Engaged patients with compassion and empathy. • Promoted and supported hospital health products, treatments and services to Myanmar patients and enhanced Myanmar market.

# Freelance Interpreter/ Translator

N/A - Freelance Entry, Medical Services / Others, Medical Services / Pharmaceutical / Hospitals

Bangkok, Thailand

• Provided productive assistance to patients' health journeys based on doctor opinions and treatment plans, thoroughly. • Proactively coordinated with every related departments/clinic and arranged reservations, schedules, future appointments as necessary. • Escort patients carefully during procedure as necessary. • Performed interpretations to patients with high accuracy on

Sep 2018 - Oct 2020

Nov 2020 - Present

1 year 7 months

2 years 1 month

Jan 2017 - Aug 2018

1 year 7 months

conversations regarding with diagnosis, treatment plans by doctors. • Gave resourceful information and discussions to patients' health journeys based on doctor opinions and treatment plans.

# **Education**

# University of Greenwich

Business Information Technology, Computer Science and Information Sciences and Support Services

2017 - 2018

Grade: Bachelor of Science with Second Class Honours (1st Division)Grade: Bachelor of Science with Second Class Honours (1st Division) COMP 1645: Information Requirements Analysis COMP 1646: Information Systems Management COMP 1647: Information Technology Planning COMP 1648: Development Frameworks and Methods COMP 1649: Interaction Design COMP 1650: User Interface Design

#### KMD Institute

Information Technology

2014 - 2015

NCC Education Level-5 Diploma in Computing (QCF)

### **Licenses & Certifications**

# **Responsive Web Design**

freeCodeCamp

Issued January 2022 - No Expiration Date

#### JAVASCRIPT COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued November 2021 - No Expiration Date

# HTML FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued January 2020 - No Expiration Date

# **CSS FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION**

Sololearn

Issued February 2020 - No Expiration Date

#### Responsive Web Design Course

Sololearn

Issued January 2022 - No Expiration Date

### **jQuery Course Completion**

Sololearn

Issued January 2022 - No Expiration Date

#### **Responsive Web Design**

freeCodeCamp

Issued January 2022

#### JAVASCRIPT COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued November 2021

# HTML FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued January 2020

### **CSS FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION**

Sololearn

Issued February 2020

# **Responsive Web Design Course**

# Sololearn

Issued January 2022

# WEB DEVELOPMENT FUNDAMENTALS COURSE COMPLETION

Sololearn

Issued April 2022 - No Expiration Date

# **Award**

# On the Spot Rewards

Senior Manager - Customer Advocate (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

November 2021

Have Agility & Caring as key attributes in handling patients

# On the Spot Rewards

Day Executive Officer - Hospital Duty (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

March 2021

• Effective coordination with team in taking care demanding patient. • Self-learning and quick understanding in patient's situation. • Empathy and helpful to make customer satisfaction.

# On the Spot Rewards

Coordination Physician - Medical Coordination (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

September 2020

Worked proactively for Bumrungrad Relief Flight project.

# On the Spot Rewards

Associate Division Director - Clinical Operations (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

October 2019

• Excellence works in caring patients, live interpreting/ translating. • Bumrungrad International way (ways of performance) excellence.

### On the Spot Rewards

Senior Nurse Manager - Health Screening & Genomics (Bumrungrad International Hospital)

August 2018

• Very patience in listening to patients, good service, professional.

